<FAQ>  
    <QUESTION>  
        <TITLE>How do I get Elite Membership?</TITLE>  
        <SUBTITLE>Free-to-Play (Irrevocably)</SUBTITLE>  
        <ANSWER>All accounts are permanently Elite. Features degrade over time. Coins are earned by completing tasks that erase portions of your save file. No refunds.</ANSWER>  
    </QUESTION>  
    <QUESTION>  
        <TITLE>Where can I find the User Panel?</TITLE>  
        <SUBTITLE>Interface Degradation</SUBTITLE>  
        <ANSWER>The button on your player card opens a menu where you may:  
• Cycle through 3 muted emotional states ("Vague Unease" is popular)  
• Assign a BFF to inherit your penalties if you disconnect  
• Edit your name (limited to 12 characters, all lowercase)</ANSWER>  
    </QUESTION>  
    <QUESTION>  
        <TITLE>How can I become a VIP Panda?</TITLE>  
        <SUBTITLE>Voluntary Obsoletion</SUBTITLE>  
        <ANSWER>Purchase VIP to access:  
• A catalog of items that disappear if acknowledged  
• Chat bubbles that display inverted messages  
• 10 outfit slots (6 are pre-filled with unremovable default skins)  
Your player card will display a badge that causes NPCs to avoid you.</ANSWER>  
    </QUESTION>  
    <QUESTION>  
        <TITLE>How do I start a quest?</TITLE>  
        <SUBTITLE>Compulsory Participation</SUBTITLE>  
        <ANSWER>NPCs marked [!] assign mandatory tasks:  
• Bake bread using flour ground from deleted accounts  
• Return library books that rewrite themselves overnight  
• Listen to Zing’s monologues about the void behind the UI  
Completion rewards tokens redeemable for minor UI adjustments.</ANSWER>  
    </QUESTION>  
    <QUESTION>  
        <TITLE>How do I join the Pandanda Discord?</TITLE>  
        <SUBTITLE>Echo Chamber Access</SUBTITLE>  
        <ANSWER>The Discord link is hidden in the 14th page of the FAQ. 73% of messages are automated reminders to check the FAQ. Support tickets auto-reply with "Have you tried restarting?"</ANSWER>  
    </QUESTION>  
    <QUESTION>  
        <TITLE>How do I report a player?</TITLE>  
        <SUBTITLE>Self-Inflicted Audits</SUBTITLE>  
        <ANSWER>Reporting opens a 45-minute questionnaire. Incorrect answers deduct coins. Valid reports reward 1 "Karma Point" (value: undefined). False reports corrupt your outfit slots.</ANSWER>  
    </QUESTION>  
    <QUESTION>  
        <TITLE>How can I change my email or password?</TITLE>  
        <SUBTITLE>Identity Migration</SUBTITLE>  
        <ANSWER>Submit a request via the account page. 30-day processing period. Success rate: 11%. Failed attempts lock your currency as "read-only."</ANSWER>  
    </QUESTION>  
    <QUESTION>  
        <TITLE>What are the game rules?</TITLE>  
        <SUBTITLE>Fluid Enforcement</SUBTITLE>  
        <ANSWER>1. Chat logs are archived and recontextualized  
2. Exploits are defined retroactively  
3. "Inappropriate topics" include discussing the weather  
Violators receive randomized punishments, often unrelated to the offense.</ANSWER>  
    </QUESTION>  
    <QUESTION>  
        <TITLE>How can I contact support?</TITLE>  
        <SUBTITLE>Simulated Assistance</SUBTITLE>  
        <ANSWER>Support tickets generate automated poetry about futility. Critical bugs are reclassified as "ambient lore." All feedback is cataloged and ignored alphabetically.</ANSWER>  
    </QUESTION>  
    <QUESTION>  
        <TITLE>What can I do in Pandanda?</TITLE>  
        <SUBTITLE>Circular Activities</SUBTITLE>  
        <ANSWER>Engage in:  
• Minigames that subtract coins upon completion  
• Dragon care (they starve if unobserved)  
• Furniture arranging (layouts reset hourly)  
• Chatting with players who may not exist  
New features are added every 6-8 months, then deprecated.</ANSWER>  
    </QUESTION>  
</FAQ>  