<FAQ>

    <QUESTION>
        <TITLE>become an Elite Member?</TITLE>
        <SUBTITLE>Elite Membership</SUBTITLE>
        <ANSWER>Some features like unlocking your tree house, buying furniture for your tree house, and buying clothes for your Panda are reserved for players who become Elite Members. 
If you would like to sign up to be an Elite Member, please visit the Membership page.
        </ANSWER>
    </QUESTION>
    <QUESTION>
        <TITLE>Ignore or report another player?</TITLE>
        <SUBTITLE>Ignoring and Reporting Players</SUBTITLE>
        <ANSWER>By clicking on another player and selecting "Ignore Player", you will have a choice to either ignore that player or report them. Both of these actions will add the player to your ignore list and you will no longer see them in Pandanda.
However, you should only report a player if you believe he or she has broken one of the Pandanda Rules. Reporting a player will send an alert to a Pandanda Moderator for investigation.</ANSWER>
    </QUESTION>
    <QUESTION>
        <TITLE>Pandanda Rules</TITLE>
        <SUBTITLE>Pandanda Rules</SUBTITLE>
        <ANSWER>Pandanda does not tolerate bad language and discussion of inappropriate topics. This includes swearing, dating chat, bullying and general disrespectful behavior towards other players. In addition it is not appropriate to discuss drug, alcohol, sex and racial topics. Players found not obeying this rule will be banned and repeated offenses will result in permanent banning.
Play it safe by never sharing your real name, address, phone number, email address, or passwords with anyone online.
Players may not use third party programs or create any programs that enable cheating in Pandanda. Use of such programs will result in permanent banning.</ANSWER>
    </QUESTION>
    <QUESTION>
        <TITLE>Report a Bug</TITLE>
        <SUBTITLE>Report a Bug</SUBTITLE>
        <ANSWER>We are always working to make Pandanda a better place. If you think you have found a bug in the game, please click the button below to submit a bug report. Your help will make Pandanda better for everyone!</ANSWER>
    </QUESTION>
    
</FAQ>