<QUESTS>
	<!-- FISHING - Fishy Joe -->
	<QUEST ID="Q001a">
		<NAME>Menace At The Beach</NAME>
		<START>NPC004</START>
		<ACTIVE>NPC004</ACTIVE>
		<END>NPC004</END>
		<TEXTSTART>
Did you hear the rumors? Pandas have said they've seen a shark swimming around at Coconut Beach scaring away the Pandas. A shark in Pandanda Land! I guess crazier things have happened. 
If you feel up for a little adventure, see if you can catch that shark and then bring it to me. 		</TEXTSTART>
		<TEXTACTIVE>You been brave enough to catch that shark at Coconut Beach? I wouldn't blame you if you're too scared.</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Take a look at those teeth! Coconut Beach is safe again! 
Here's a little something for your bravery.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q001b">
	    	<NAME>Salmon Run</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC004</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC004</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC004</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Hey, I'm glad you stopped by. I've got a huge order of salmon I need to deliver and I'm a few fish short. You'd be a real life saver if you could bring me 5 salmon by the day's end.
Coconut Beach is the perfect place to fish for the salmon I need.
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>Have you had a chance to catch those salmon for me? Head over to Coconut Beach and get fishing, I've got to get that order delivered!</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Whew! Just in the nick of time! 
Thanks for your help, here's some coins for the fish.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q001c">
	    	<NAME>Old Muddy</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC004</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC004</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC004</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Have you heard the legend of Old Muddy? He's the most clever and elusive fish in the Fishing Hole lake. I've spent half my life trying to fish him up.  
I'd give a pretty penny to whoever could catch that old fella.
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>One of these days Old Muddy will meet his match!</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Well I'll be. I never thought I'd see the day when someone would out-smart Old Muddy!
Here's your reward as promised.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q001d">
	    	<NAME>Something Fishy</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC004</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC004</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC004</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
I was out on the lake here the other day fishing when something big grabbed my line. It nearly toppled my boat before yanking my fishing pole right out of my hands! That was my favorite fishing pole too!
Not sure what it was, but it must have been huge! If you can catch whatever it was I'll pay you a handsome reward!
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>Have you caught anything in the lake that's big enough to steal my fishing pole?</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Woo wee! That's a big one! I'll bet that's the fish that stole my fishing pole!
Here's your reward for catching him!
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q001e">
	    <NAME>Lobster Dinner</NAME>
	    <START>NPC004</START>
	    <ACTIVE>NPC004</ACTIVE>
	    <END>NPC004</END>
	    <TEXTSTART>Seems like no matter how many lobsters I catch, Pandas always want more! I'm sold out already today! Could you head over to Coconut Beach and catch me 5 fresh lobsters?
Here, take my lobster trap, that fishing pole won't do you any good.  When you see a lobster swimming around in the water, sneak up on 'em and throw down that trap! </TEXTSTART>
	    <TEXTACTIVE>How you getting along with those lobsters? Not as easy as catching minnows. </TEXTACTIVE>
	    <TEXTEND>Ah, look at those beauties! Umm, umm, they look tasty! Here's your reward for a job well done!</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q001f">
	    	<NAME>Mail Order Mishap</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC004</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC004</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC004</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Hey, glad you're here! I ordered some new fishing gear and it seems the packages got mixed up and were delivered to different parts of Pandanda Land. 
You'd be doing me a huge favor if you could find all my packages and bring them to me. I know one of them ended up at The Big Scoop run by McWiggles. Not sure where the others ended up. 
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
Have you found my packages yet? I'm anxious to try out that new fishing gear.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Ah, you found them. Looks like everything is accounted for. 
Here's some coins to show my appreciation!
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	
	<!-- Lisa -->
	<QUEST ID="Q002a">
	    	<NAME>Lost Jewelry!</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC002</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC002</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC002</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Help! I've lost my favorite necklace and bracelet! They're my favorite jewelry in the whole world and there's no way I could ever replace them. 
I think I lost my necklace when I was at the beach the other day. But my bracelet probably fell off when I was indoors somewhere.
Could you please go look for them? I'd be really sad if they're gone forever!
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
I'm so sad without my jewelry! Have you found anything? 
Be sure to check Coconut Beach for my necklace and The Purple Door, The Big Scoop, and the Book Nook for my bracelet.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
You found them! Thank you so much! 
You're my new best friend, just don't tell Sara!
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q002b">
	    	<NAME>You're Sweet!</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC002</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC002</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC002</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Oh, could you help me? My father gave me a handful of candy earlier but now they're all gone! They must have fallen out of my pocket while I was skipping.
Could you help me look for them? They could be anywhere but I'm sure you could find them if anyone could! You'd be a real friend for helping me!
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
Any luck finding my candy? I hope someone didn't eat them, that would be awful!
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Yay, you found them! Thanks a lot! I think I'll eat some now to celebrate.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q002c">
	    	<NAME>The Ghost on Misty Hill</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC002</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC002</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC015</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Have you seen the haunted house on Misty Hill? I have a friend that lives there but he's a little shy around strangers and will only talk to you if you bring him some Ghost Flowers that can be found on Misty Hill. To get to Misty Hill, travel through the back of the woods in Pawthorne Forest.
When you get to the haunted house you'll have to take a secret passage to the Haunted Hallway. That's where you'll find him.
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>Did you take some Ghost Flowers to my friend? Make sure to tell him they're from me!</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Ah, a visitor! And you brought me Ghost Flowers from Lisa! These are my favorite. 
Please tell her to come and visit me soon. 
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q002d">
	    	<NAME>Late Fees Again?</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC002</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC002</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC002</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Please help me! I have 4 books that are due back to the library tomorrow and I don't know where they are! If I don't return them on time I'll have to pay a late fee!
I remember reading a book at The Den club house in Pawthorne Forest and another at the Book Nook. I'm not sure where the others might be. I'm sure you could find them for me!
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
Have you seen my library books? I can't afford any more late fees!
I wish I could remember where I left them all.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>Oh great! Thanks a lot! That old Panda at the library won't be mad at me now.</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q002f">
	    	<NAME>Joe Needs Worms!</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC002</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC002</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC004</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Do you know Joe who works over at the Fishing Hole? He asked me to collect a bunch of worms for him to be used as fishing bait but I totally forgot!
Could you help me out and find 5 Small Worms and take them to him? He was going to pay me, so you can keep the coins. You can find worms in Pawthorne Forest, Darby Field, and here in Shady Glen.
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
Did you find those worms for Fishy Joe yet? I don't want to get in trouble!
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Ah, some new fishing bait. Did Lisa give these to you? 
Here's the coins I owe her and tell her thanks for me!
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q002g">
	    	<NAME>Runaway Dragons</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC002</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC002</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC002</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Oh please help me! I was pet sitting for some Pandas and while I was out walking the dragons they got off their leashes and escaped! I'll lose my pet sitting job if I cannot find them!
If you happen to find any while you're out walking around please bring them back to me! There are 4 dragons missing all together. 
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
Any luck finding the dragons? If I don't return them to their owners soon, I'll lose my pet sitting job!
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Oh thank you! You really are the nicest Panda! 
Here, you can have these coins for your help.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	
	<!-- McWiggles -->
	<QUEST ID="Q003a">
	    	<NAME>Strawberry Cream Swirl</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC001</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC001</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC001</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Ah, so glad you're here! I'm running low on ingredients for my famous Strawberry Cream Swirl. It's my best seller, you know.
Let's see... I'll need a Quart of Cream, 1 Large Sugar Beet from the Orchard, and 3 Large Strawberries. Farmer Dan will have the cream and Harvest Grove is the best place to pick strawberries. Hurry along now.
		</TEXTSTART>
		<TEXTACTIVE>Have you had a chance to gather those ingredients for me? Pandas are clamoring for my strawberry ice cream!</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Excellent, exactly what I needed! These strawberries look mighty fresh!
Here, take some coins for your trouble.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q003b">
	    	<NAME>Sweet and Sour</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC003</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC003</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC001</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Hi! I was supposed to get some items for McWiggles who works at The Big Scoop, but I completely forgot. Something about Lemon ice cream...
I think he needed a Quart of Cream, a Large Sugar Beet, and some Large Lemons. Would you collect those items and take them to him for me? Farmer Dan should have the cream for sale and you can get sugar beets from the Orchard.
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>Did you get the items for McWiggles? Don't tell him I forgot about it!</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Ah, just in time. I was almost out of my lemon ice cream! 
I was beginning to think Paige forgot about me.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q003c">
	    	<NAME>A New Taste Sensation</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC001</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC001</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC001</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Ah, you're just in time to help me with my latest ice cream creation! It's got a little bit of cinnamon, a touch of spice root, and ... well, the rest is my little secret. Although, I do need a few more ingredients if you have the time. 
If you could bring me a Quart of Cream, 2 Large Sugar Beets from the Orchard, and 2 Fresh Honey Combs from Pawthorne Forest, I'd be forever grateful! Farmer Dan will sell you the cream.
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>How are you coming along with those ingredients? I know this will be my greatest creation yet!</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Splendid! These look nice and fresh! You might have a future in culinary arts. 
Here's some compensation for your effort.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q003d">
	    	<NAME>Fresh from the Farm</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC014</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC014</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC001</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Howdy! Feel like makin' a delivery for me? McWiggles, who runs The Big Scoop, asked me to get a few supplies for him but I got busy with other things.
Now where did I put that list? Ah, here we are, he needs a Quart of Cream, a Large Sugar Beet, and 3 Sweet Cherries. I reckon you can find the cherries and sugar beet at the Orchard easy enough, then talk to Farmer Dan for the cream. Best be runnin' off now, don't want to keep McWiggles waiting.
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
You get those supplies for McWiggles yet? I know he was in a hurry to get them.
You'll find him in The Big Scoop ice cream parlor when you're done. 
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Ah, the supplies I needed from Farmer Ned! Looks like everything is here, thanks.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q003e">
	    	<NAME>The Sugar Toothed Tailor</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC008</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC008</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC001</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Greetings! I was getting some ice cream from McWiggles the other day and heard him say he is trying to come up with new recipes for ice cream flavors. 
I bet if you took him a some Fresh Honey Comb, a few Large Sugar Beets, and a couple Large Blueberries, he could make something really tasty. You'll find the honey comb in Pawthorne Forest, sugar beets in the Orchard, and head over to Harvest Grove for the blueberries.
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
Did you get those ingredients for McWiggles yet?
Once you have them you'll probably find him in The Big Scoop ice cream parlor.
I can't wait to see what new flavors he comes up with.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Ah, more flavors for my ice cream experiments! 
Here, have some coins for your kindness.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q003f">
	    	<NAME>Berrylicious</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC001</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC001</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC001</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Nice to see you again! I've heard there are delicious looking Red Raspberries growing over in Harvest Grove. I think they would make an excellent addition to my ice cream selection, don't you?
Would you mind picking some Red Raspberries and bringing them to me? I'll gladly pay you for you time. I could also use a Large Sugar Beet from the Orchard and a Quart of Cream from Farmer Dan if it's no trouble.
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
Did you find the Red Raspberries over at Harvest Grove? I can't wait to whip up some a new ice cream flavor.
Don't forget the cream and sugar beet.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Ah, thank you! I'll start work on my raspberry ice cream first thing tomorrow. 
Here's your payment. 
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	
	<!-- Tammy Tomato -->
	<QUEST ID="Q004a">
	    	<NAME>A Green Thumb</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC005</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC005</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC005</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Hi, would you like to help me with some gardening? I have several gardens set up at the Orchard, Darby Field, Shady Glen, and Harvest Grove that are ready for planting.
Take these flower seeds and plant them in each of the gardens. Make sure you get them all! Come back and see me when you're done.
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
Did you plant all the flower seeds at my gardens? They will be so pretty!
You can find the gardens set up at the Orchard, Darby Field, Shady Glen, and Harvest Grove.
 		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Thanks! You've been a great help. 
I can't wait for the flowers bloom!
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q004b">
	    	<NAME>The Thirsty Flowers</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC005</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC005</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC005</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Would you like to help me out with my flowers? They're starting to droop and need watering. I'd do it myself but don't have time to get to them today. 
Take this watering can and visit my flowers in the Orchard, Darby Field, Shady Glen, and Harvest Grove. Be sure to bring my watering can back when you're done!
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
Make sure you water all the flowers really well. I'm sure they are thirsty!
You can find the drooping flowers at the Orchard, Darby Field, Shady Glen, and Harvest Grove.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>Thanks for your help! I'll go by later to see how they look.</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q004c">
	    	<NAME>A Bouquet for Tammy</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC005</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC005</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC005</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Have you seen my flower gardens? They are in full bloom right now and so beautiful! Would you be so kind as to pick some flowers from each of my gardens and bring them to me?
You'll find the flowers in the Orchard, Darby Field, Shady Glen, and Harvest Grove.		
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
Be careful when picking the flowers, they can be very delicate.
You can find the flowers blooming at the Orchard, Darby Field, Shady Glen, and Harvest Grove.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>These are beautiful! Thank you for your help!</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q004d">
	    	<NAME>Making Compost</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC005</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC005</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC005</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
I've found a great way to fertilize my garden soil by adding organic compost. I make my own compost but I could use help getting a few more materials like leaves, grass clippings, and old newspapers to mix in.
You can find Grass Clippings in Darby Field, Leaves in Pawthorne Forest, and Newspapers in one of the towns. 
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
Did you gather the compost materials I need for my organic compost? I'll shred them up and add start a new compost bin.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>Great! Thanks for your help, these will do wonderfully.</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q004e">
	    	<NAME>Enriching the Soil</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC005</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC005</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC005</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Hi, I've got some organic compost that needs to be added to my gardens. Would you mind helping me out, if you're not too busy?
All you need to do is visit my gardens at the Orchard, Darby Field, Shady Glen, and Harvest Grove and add the compost to the Garden Soil. Be sure to bring back the wheelbarrow once you've finished.
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
Did you add the compost to all of the gardens? The compost needs to be added before I can plant any more flowers.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>Thanks! I'm sure the enriched soil will really help my flowers!</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>

	<!-- Steve McClean -->
	<QUEST ID="Q005a">
	    	<NAME>Soiled Again</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC006</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC006</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC006</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
What a fine day we're having! If you're not too busy, or planning to take a nap, perhaps you could help me with my environmental studies of Pandanda Land.
I've placed yellow flags in several locations around Pandanda where I'd like you to collect soil samples. Once you have them all bring them back here. Do you think you could manage that? 
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
I need those soil samples so I can perform my environmental tests.
Look for the yellow flags like the ones in Darby Field and Pawthorne Forest.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Ah, thank you! These will do nicely. 
Here's some coins for your assistance.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q005b">
	    	<NAME>It's Always Sunny in Pandanda</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC006</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC006</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC006</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Nice weather we're having today! I like to keep track of weather patterns across Pandanda, a little hobby of mine. I could use a little help if you've got the time.
I've marked out several locations around Pandanda where I'd like you to take weather readings. Take this weather device with you and place it down on the marked spots like the one in West Market Street.  Bring it back once you've finished, it's the only weather device I have!
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
Did you take those weather readings yet? You'll find one of the lighted green X markings in West Market Street to get you started.
Please be careful with my weather device, it's expensive!
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Done already? I'll process the weather data when I get back to my tree house. 
Thanks again!
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q005c">
	    	<NAME>Make Sure it's Pure</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC006</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC006</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC006</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
All this recycling got me thinking of how to reduce plastic bottles, so I've been working on my own water purifier. But I need more water samples to test it out. You look like you could use some work, what do you say?
Head over to the Fishing Hole and Coconut Beach and bring me back 2 water samples from each location. You'll see a yellow bobber where to take the samples from. Make sure you keep them separated! 
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>My water purifier might just put an end to all these plastic bottles.</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>Ah, there you are. And you got the water samples, great! 
I'll let you know when my purifier is up and running.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q005d">
	    	<NAME>Sounds of Serenity</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC006</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC006</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC006</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Is there anything more peaceful than the sounds of the ocean? I'm putting together a "Serene Sounds of Pandanda" cd to help me relax after a hard day. Think you could help me collect the sound samples?
I've marked out some spots around Pandanda that provide the perfect tranquil sounds I'm looking for. All you have to do is take this recorder and place it on the marked spots in each location, then bring it back when you're finished.
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
Hey, how are the sound recordings coming along? 
The best spots to record are Coconut Beach, The Fishing Hole, Shady Glen, Pawthorne Forest, and Harvest Grove. 
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Ah, wonderful you're back. I'll take a listen to these this evening. 
Have a few coins for your help.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q005e">
	    	<NAME>Cleaning Up the Lake</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC006</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC006</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC006</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
I heard some Pandas were fishing over at the Fishing Hole and fished up some old junk out of the lake! We all gotta do our part to keep Pandanda clean. Feel like helping out?
Head over to the Fishing Hole and fish up 3 pieces of junk out of the lake. Bring em back and I'll make sure they get disposed of properly. 
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
Were you able to fish up any junk from the lake? I'm sure the fish will appreciate it too!
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Look at this old junk. Well, you've done your part and the lake is clean once again. 
Here's some coins for you help!
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>


	<!-- Jim -->
	<QUEST ID="Q006a">
	    	<NAME>Amethyst in the Mist</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC007</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC007</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC007</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Hey there. I'm always on the lookout for rare minerals and gemstones, but today I need something specific. I've heard of some Pandas finding Amethyst in Pawthorne Forest and Small Silver Ore up on Misty Hill. 
Bring me some of each and I'll pay you handsomely for your troubles.
		</TEXTSTART>
		<TEXTACTIVE>How's it going with that Amethyst and Small Silver Ore? Is it true there are ghosts on Misty Hill?</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
There we go. Look at those beauties! 
Here's some coins for your help. 
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q006b">
	    	<NAME>The Azurite Ring</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC007</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC007</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC007</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Hey, you got time to help out a fellow Panda? I'm supposed to make a custom ring for a client and they specifically asked for gold plating with azurite gemstones. Problem is, I'm all out of azurite and gold.
If you bring me some Azurite Ore from Shady Glen and Small Gold Ore from Harvest Grove, I can pay you for your time. 		
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
Did you get the gold and azurite yet?
I'm supposed to have the ring ready by tomorrow. 
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
You're back! And you've got the stuff I need, excellent! 
Here's the payment we agreed to.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q006c">
	    	<NAME>Silver and Gold (Sans the Gold)</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC007</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC007</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC007</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
I'm always in need of Silver Ore that I can smelt down and use to make jewelry. Rumor has it there's plenty of Silver Ore to be mined up on Misty Hill. Of course there's also the rumor that Misty Hill is haunted! I'd go myself but, uh, I'm busy.
Think you could bring me 5 Small Silver Ore? You'll need a rock hammer to mine the silver. If you don't have one, I'll sell you one for a fair price.
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>Had any luck mining that Silver Ore? I'm getting low on silver and people always want more jewelry.</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Ah, this will last me a while. 
I hope those ghosts on Misty Hill didn't cause you too much trouble.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q006d">
	    	<NAME>Gold Moon</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC007</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC007</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC007</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
What do you know about Moonstone? It's one of my most popular requests when making custom jewelry for Pandas. It'd be a great help if you could bring me some. Oh, and while you're helping out, might as well bring me a few Small Gold Ore as well.
I hear Pawthorne Forest is a good place to find Moonstone and of course everyone knows about the Small Gold Ore in Harvest Grove, but uh, you didn't hear that from me.		
		</TEXTSTART>
		<TEXTACTIVE>Yep, Moonstone is really popular these days. Not really my favorite though. I prefer diamonds.</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Let's see what you got. Looks good! You're a hard worker. 
Come by again tomorrow and I might have some more work for you.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q006e">
	    	<NAME>A Tale of Two Opals</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC007</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC007</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC007</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Hey, wondering if you could help me out? I'm making a bracelet for my sweetheart and I want it to be really special. She loves Opal! Now, the thing to know is that there's a couple kinds of Opal that can be found in Pandanda Land and to make this ring, I'll need both Light Opal and Dark Opal.
What do you say, could you get those for me? The best place to mine for Opal is in Darby Field. Just watch out for those rabbits!
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
I've got the bracelet crafted, once you bring me the Opal I can set the stones.
You can mine the Opal in Darby Field.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Perfect, these look terrific. This is going to be the best bracelet I've ever made! 
Here's some coins for your help!
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>

	<!-- Dan -->
	<QUEST ID="Q007a">
	    	<NAME>Flaky Crust is a Must</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC010</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC010</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC010</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Ummm, you know what would make today even better? Some homemade apple turnovers! Those tender apples and cinnamon in a flaky crust, my mouth is watering already!
All I'd need is a Small Bag of Flour from Farmer Ned, a few Small Brown Eggs from his barn, and 2 Juicy Apples which I'm sure you can find in the Orchard. Think you could handle that?
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
I'd sure appreciate you getting me those items so I could make my apple turnovers. Wrangling these bunnies really works up my appetite!
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Ahh, that's the stuff! These will make a splendid dessert!
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q007b">
	    	<NAME>Bye Bye Blackberry</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC010</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC010</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC010</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
You know what's better than blackberry pie? Me neither. Of course it takes the freshest ingredients to make the freshest pies. 
Think you could rustle up some Blackberries from Harvest Grove, a Small Bag of Flour from Farmer Ned and a Small Brown Egg from his Barn? 
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>I sure do appreciate your help today. Nice to know there's helpful Pandas around like yourself.</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Well that was speedy! Here's some coins to cover the cost of the flour.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q007c">
	    	<NAME>Peachy Keen</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC010</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC010</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC010</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Do you like peaches? I do! And I make a great Peach Cobbler if I do say so myself! Of course, I'll need a few items before I can bake some up.
I reckon I'll need a Small Bag of Flour from Farmer Ned, a couple of Small Brown Eggs from Ned's Barn, and 2 Fuzzy Peaches from the Orchard. Could you help me out?
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>Did you get those items for the Peach Cobbler? My stomach is rumblin'!</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Aye now, those look mighty fresh! Me and my stomach thank you.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q007d">
	    	<NAME>Famous Blueberry Pie</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC010</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC010</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC010</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
I'm making my famous Farmer Dan Blueberry Pie but I'm missing a few ingredients and haven't had time to go shopping. Would you be a true friend and get them for me?
Let's see, I'll need a Small Bag of Flour from Farmer Ned, a Small Brown Egg from his Barn, and 3 Hardy Blueberries from Harvest Grove. I think that should do it. 
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>Did you find the pie ingredients I need? Umm, I can taste it already!</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Yee haw, those look tasty! I hope it wasn't too difficult to get them. 
Here's a few coins for your help!
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q007e">
	    	<NAME>Bring Home the Rhubarb</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC010</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC010</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC010</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
The Missus wants me to bring home some items so she can make a rhubarb pie for dessert. It's not my favorite but I can't complain when she's doing the cookin'.  
You have time to fetch a few items for me? I reckon I'll need a Small Brown Egg from Farmer Ned's Barn, some Rhubarb from Harvest Grove, and a Small Bag of Flour. Farmer Ned will have that for sale.
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>Don't be too long getting those items. I'll be in a heap of trouble if I go home empty handed.</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Ahh, you're a life saver you are. These are just what I needed.
Here's some coins for your help.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q007f">
	    	<NAME>Bunnies on a Diet</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC010</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC010</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC010</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Howdy! I've been noticing my bunnies acting a bit sluggish lately. Think it's time to mix up their diet with a new mixture of vegetables. Do you have time to help me out?
I need a Large Radish and 2 Red Cabbage from Harvest Grove and a few Purple Carrots which you can find right here in Darby Field. I'll blend them together for the bunnies myself.		
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
Were you able to get all the vegetables for my new bunny diet mix? I can't have them sleeping all day!
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Yee haw, this will do nicely! I appreciate your help and I'm sure the bunnies will as well.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>

	<!-- Izzy -->
	<QUEST ID="Q008a">
	    	<NAME>Wall of Fish</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC012</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC012</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC012</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Hi! I've been thinking about adding some new fish to my giant wall tank here in the store.  More brightly colored fish would really spruce up the place.
Could you head over to Coconut Beach and catch me some Orange Clownfish, Regal Tang, and Yellow Longnose Butterfly fish? They would make a great addition to my collection!
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>My aquarium really needs a makeover. Have you caught any fish for me?</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Cool! These fish are just what I needed. Now I just need to clean out the tank. 
Have some coins for your help.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q008b">
	    	<NAME>Top Dollar Fish</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC012</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC012</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC009</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Ah, glad you stopped by! Mr. Elmhurst was in the other day looking for some new fish for his aquarium. I know he would pay top dollar for them.
If you'd like to make a few coins, catch a Yellow Longnose Butterfly fish from Coconut Beach, then head over to the Fishing Hole and catch 2 Calico Goldfish and a Violet Perch. Once you have all the fish take them to Mr. Elmhurst on West Market Street.
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
I know Mr. Elmhurst will be really excited to get those fish. 
If you need a fishing pole, Fishy Joe sells them for a fair price.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Ah, wonderful! I can't wait to add these to my aquarium. 
Here's some coins for the fish.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q008c">
	    	<NAME>Fish for Fitch</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC012</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC012</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC008</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Oh dear! The proprietor of Clothing Co., Fitch, has ordered some new fish for an aquarium he just bought but I don't have the fish he wanted!
I tell you what, if you take him 2 Golden Addis Butterfly fish, 2 Wakin Goldfish, and a Black Angelfish you can keep the coins he gives you. You can catch the Gold Addis from Coconut Beach and the others from the Fishing Hole.
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>Did you catch those fish for Fitch yet? Don't forget to collect the coins he owes for them.</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
My new fish! They look great! Tell Izzy I said thanks! 
Oh, and here's the coins I owe her.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q008d">
	    	<NAME>Fish Make Great Gifts</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC012</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC012</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC001</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Do you know McWiggles who runs the Ice Cream Shop? He wanted to buy some fish for his daughter Lisa as a surprise. Let's see, he was interested in getting a few Maroon Clownfish, an Orange Clownfish, and some Violet Perch for her.
I'm sure you can catch the clownfish from Coconut Beach but you'll want to head to the Fishing Hole to catch the perch. Once you have the fish, take them over to McWiggles in the Ice Cream Shop. 
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
Once you've caught the fish take them over to McWiggles at The Big Scoop. I'm sure he'll want to wrap them up.	    	
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Oh my! These fish are terrific! I'm sure Lisa will love these.
Let's hope she takes good care of them.	    	
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q008e">
	    	<NAME>Clowns and Angels</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC012</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC012</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC012</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Hi! Would you have some time to help me replenish some of my fish supply? The clownfish and angelfish are flying off the shelves! I can hardly keep them in stock.
I need 2 Orange Clownfish which can be caught from Coconut Beach and 3 Black Angelfish from over at the Fishing Hole. Hurry back, I'll probably have them sold by the time you return.
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>Have you caught any of the fish I need? I do hate to send customers home empty handed.</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Great timing! I have a customer coming in this afternoon to pick them up! 
Here's some coins for your help.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>

<!-- Maggie -->
	<QUEST ID="Q009a">
	    	<NAME>Watch Your Step</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC024</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC024</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC024</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Howdy! I sure could use some help if you don't mind getting your paws dirty. All these horses around town have been making a bit of a smell, if you know what I mean. 
Think you could stop by Bear Hollow, East and West Market Street and do a little sanitation clean up? Head on back here when you're done.
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>How's that horse clean up going? I'd hate for any pandas to accidentally step in something.</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Got the towns all cleaned up? I'm sure everyone appreciates having clean streets to walk on. Just be sure to wash your paws!
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q009b">
	    	<NAME>Horses Wear Shoes Too</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC024</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC024</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC007</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Glad you stopped by. My horses need new shoes! Jim is going to make some for me but needs the raw materials first. Would you be interested in gathering some Small Iron Ore and Small Bauxite Ore for me? 
Once you have them take the ore over to Jim on West Market Street and he'll know what to do. You'll find the iron in Harvest Grove and the bauxite at Misty Hill.
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>Have you gathered the iron and bauxite ore yet? Take them over to Jim on West Market Street when you have them.</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Ah, these must be for the horse shoes Maggie needs. Great, I'll be able to make a lot of shoes from this much ore.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q009c">
	    	<NAME>Where's the Hay?</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC024</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC024</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC024</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Hey darling, would you like to help me out? I was supposed to get a delivery of hay bales but when the tractor showed up the hay bales were gone. They must have fallen off along the way.
Could you go out and look for the Hay Bales? If you can find them and bring them to me I'll make sure you're rewarded with some coins.
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>Any luck finding those Hay Bales? They must have fallen off the tractor outside somewhere.</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Super, you found them all! I knew I could count on such a wonderful Panda as you.
Here's some coins for your help.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q009d">
	    	<NAME>Equine Snacks</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC024</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC024</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC024</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Hey there, glad you stopped by. I like to feed my horses a special treat every now and then. They get tired of eating oats all time.
Would you go out and get me 3 Fresh Apples and 2 Nutritious Carrots? You'll find the apples at the Orchard and Darby Field has some of the best carrots around. 
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>Hey, did you get the Fresh Apples and Nutritious Carrots yet? My horses will be thrilled to get a tasty snack.</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Back so soon? These look fantastic! My horses and I thank you for your help!
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	
	<!-- Halloween -->
	<QUEST ID="Q051a">
	    	<NAME>Eyes on the Prize</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC016</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC016</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC016</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Boo! Ah, I see you don't frighten easily. Good, I am in need of your assistance. I find that I am running low on Ghoul Eyes. What do I need them for? Never you mind. Suffice it to say, I need them and that should be good enough for you. 
If you bring me 5 Ghoul Eyes I will reward you for your service. You should readily find Ghoul Eyes in Pawthorne Forest or Misty Hill.
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
Have you returned with my Ghoul Eyes? No? Well then, might I suggest you go and look for them. 
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Splendid, splendid! These will do nicely. 
Ah yes, enjoy these coins for a such a fine job.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q051b">
	    	<NAME>Wicked Brew</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC016</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC016</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC016</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Ah, you again! Surely, you have time to help me? I have several cauldrons dispersed throughout these lands that need attending. Take these items and add them to each of the cauldrons. 
There are 5 cauldrons in all and I'll know if you skip one, so do not try to trick me. Hurry now, do this for me and return when you are done!
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
Have you attended all of my cauldrons yet? Make sure you add those ingredients evenly in each one. 
Return to me when you have finished.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Ah, you have returned. I trust there were no problems? Of course not, you're an honest Panda.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q051c">
	    	<NAME>Bat Wing Stew</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC016</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC016</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC016</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Greetings Panda! Perhaps you could help me? I'm preparing a Spicy Bat Wing Stew for my fellow ghosts. And I'm in dire need of more bat wings! 
You will find bats often asleep hanging from buildings and other large structures. Bring me 4 Bats for my concoction and some Strong Spices from your Farmer Ned. Go now, time is of the essence!
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
I need those bat wings and spices! If they aren't added at the right time they stew will be ruined!
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Ah, just in the nick of time. I underestimated you, Panda. You are trustworthy indeed!
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	
	<QUEST ID="Q052a">
	    	<NAME>Chocolate Bars</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC003</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC003</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC003</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Hi! With all these Pandas out trick or treating for  candy, sometimes their pumpkins overflow and candy drops onto the ground. 
I like all candy but Chocolate Bars are my favorite. If you find any Chocolate Bars as you're walking around Pandanda, I'll trade you some coins for them.
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>Did you find any Chocolate Bars? You should find them on the ground just like the Halloween candy hidden around Pandanda.</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Thank you! You're a great friend for getting these for me. Here's the coins as promised.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q052b">
	    	<NAME>Peanut Butter Bars</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC009</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC009</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC009</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
I've got a confession to make. I love Peanut Butter Bars. The way they mix that perfect balance of chocolate and peanut butter, ummm, ummm!
If you happen to come across any Peanut Butter Bars while you're out looking for candy, I'd sure appreciate it you could bring me some. You can find Peanut Butter Bars anywhere you find other candy.
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>How's the search going? I can't wait to bite in to a Peanut Butter Bar. I'm sure you can find some mixed in with all the other candy placed around Pandanda.</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Wonderful! I'll enjoy these after dinner. Take some coins for the candy.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q052c">
	    	<NAME>Caramel Bars</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC008</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC008</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC008</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Hey there! I've seen Pandas wearing some really great costumes this year. But Halloween is just about dressing up in costumes, it's about candy too! Umm, there's not anything much better than a Caramel Bar!
Would you collect 5 Caramel Bars for me? I'm sure with all the trick or treating going on you'll find plenty. 
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>Did you find any Caramel Bars? You should be able to find them any place where you find Halloween candy.</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Oh boy, look at those mouth watering Caramel Bars! Thanks so much for your help.
Here's a few coins for helping out.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	
	
	<!-- Thanksgiving / Christmas -->
	<QUEST ID="Q055a">
	    	<NAME>Turkey Feathers</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC003</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC003</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC003</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Hi there! I've been try to collect turkey feathers to make a ceremonial headdress but at this rate I won't have enough. 
If you happen to come across any Turkey Feathers as you travel around Pandanda please pick them up and bring them to me. You'd be helping me out a lot and I'll be glad to pay you for them.
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
Have you had any luck finding the Turkey Feathers? I won't be able to complete my headdress without them.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Thank you! You're a great friend for getting these for me. 
Here's the coins as promised.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q055b">
	    	<NAME>Apple Cider</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC003</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC003</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC001</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Hi! I heard McWiggles is planning to make some of his famous apple cider. It's a great way to keep warm on a cold autumn evening and tastes great! I know he  could use some more apples if you're not busy.
I'm sure if you took him 4 Small Apples from the Orchard and some Cinnamon Spice, he'd reward you for your help. Farmer Ned should have Cinnamon Spice for sale this time of year.
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
Have you collected the apples and cinnamon for McWiggles yet? I can't wait for him to make more of that delicious apple cider.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Ah, thank you! I was just about to make a new batch of apple cider and was running low on supplies. 
Enjoy these coins for all your help.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q055c">
	    	<NAME>Pumpkin Pie</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC010</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC010</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC010</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
It's the holiday season here in Pandanda and I like to bake up some homemade Pumpkin Pie to help celebrate. If you're up for a little work, I'll need some Small Pumpkins, Cinnamon Spice, and a Medium Sugar Beet to get started. 
You'll find the best Small Pumpkins over in Harvest Grove or Shady Glen and I'm sure Farmer Ned has some Cinnamon Spice for sale. Sugar Beets can be found in the Orchard.
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
Did you get me those ingredients yet? Pumpkin Pie waits for no Panda, or so they say. 
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Ahh, those look like some might fine pumpkins! This may be my best pie yet! Much obliged!
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q055d">
	    	<NAME>Chilly The Snowman</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC003</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC003</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC019</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Hey! Have you spoken with Chilly the Snowman yet? He needs a constant supply of new snowballs to keep him looking his best.
If you find any good mounds of snow around be sure to create some snowballs and take them to him. You can find him on West Market Street.
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
Did you collect any snowballs for Chilly? I'd hate to see him melt away!
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
More snowballs! I'll just stick those right over here. 
Ah, I'm feeling better now. Thank you! 
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	
	
	<!-- Christmas -->
	<QUEST ID="Q056a">
	    	<NAME>Tree Delivery</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC009</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC009</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC009</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Ah, greetings! I wonder if you could help me spread some holiday cheer around Pandanda Land. I have a bunch of trees that need to be set up and you look like just the Panda to help.
Deliver these trees to Clothing Co., The Purple Door, The Den, Book Nook, Farmer Ned's Barn, and The Big Scoop. There should be tree stands on the floor where you need to place them. Come back to me when you're done for your reward.
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
Have you delivered those trees yet? I'm sure they will add lots of festive cheer for everyone who sees them.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
So you got them all set up? Great work! Here's some coins to show my appreciation.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q056b">
	    	<NAME>The Missing Ornaments</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC009</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC009</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC009</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Greetings to you! Would you happen to have a few minutes to spare? I was gathering all my tree ornaments and it appears I may have lost a few of them. 
I would be greatly obliged if you could take a look around Pandanda for the ornaments and bring me any that you stumble upon. 
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
Any luck find my lost tree decorations? I would start by searching Pawthorne Forest. The trees won't be nearly as festive without decorations.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Ah ha! Fantastic, you've found them. I knew you could do it!
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q056c">
	    	<NAME>Decorating The Trees</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC009</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC009</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC009</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Happy Holidays! I hope you're getting into the holiday spirit. Would you mind helping me decorate some of the trees around Pandanda?
Here, take these ornaments and place them on the trees in Clothing Co., The Purple Door, The Den, Book Nook, Farmer Ned's Barn, and The Big Scoop. Return to me once you've finished and I'll reward you with some coins.
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
How's the tree decorating going? I hope they spread some cheer to other Pandas!
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Done already? You're a very speedy helper! Here's some coins as promised.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	
	<!-- March of the Snowmen -->
	<QUEST ID="Q060a">
	    	<NAME>Snow Fort Reinforcements!</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC009</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC009</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC009</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Ah, greetings! With all the snowmen running around here, I figure it's safest to stay in this snow fort. Trouble is, it takes a lot of snow to maintain. Maybe you could help me out with that.
We'll need some Snow Blocks to reinforce the walls. The best way to make a Snow Block is to find a nice lump of snow and shape it out of that. Bring me 5 Snow Blocks and I'll make it worth your time.
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
Have you had any luck finding the Snow Blocks? This fort won't last very long with out reinforcements.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Ah, you've done me a huge favor friend and I won't soon forget it.
Here's some coins for your help.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q060b">
	    	<NAME>Keep the Fires Burning</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC003</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC003</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC003</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Hi! I've been put in charge of making sure there's plenty of firewood for the fire pits at the Fishing Hole and Coconut Beach. It's a big job and I could use a little help if you've got the time.
I still need a little more Firewood and some Newspaper that I could use as kindling. You'll find Firewood in Pawthorne Forest and probably some Newspaper Kindling in one of the towns.
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
Have you collected the Firewood and Newspaper Kindling yet? I know there's going to be a lot of Pandas around the fire pits tonight!
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Thank you! I'll deliver these to make sure all the Pandas stay warm tonight. 
Here's coins for all your help.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q061a">
	    	<NAME>Snowman Accessories</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC002</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC002</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC002</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Hey! Isn't all this snow wonderful? I'm thinking about building some snowmen but I still need some items to dress them. 
I'll need some Charcoal which can be found in Pawthorne Forest or Misty Hill and a Carrot from Darby Field. I left my Scarf in the Book Nook that could be used and I remember seeing a Top Hat in the Den Tree House in Pawthorne Forest. I knew you would help me!
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
Did you get the decorations for the snowmen yet? I'll wait until you return before I start building them.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Thanks! You're a true friend. I'll get started on the snowmen first thing tomorrow!
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q061b">
	    	<NAME>X Marks the Snowman</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC002</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC002</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC002</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Hey again! I was just about to go out and build some snowmen. Would you want to help out? 
I've marked out places in the locations where I want to build them. Maybe you could go ahead and get started? Head to Darby Field first so you'll know what to look for. Just go find those spots and stack up a snowman base. I'll do the decorating.
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
Did you find those spots I marked out for the snowmen? I can't decorate until you've stacked the snowmen.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Really, you finished? Wow, you're fast! I'll head out shortly and decorate them. 
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q061c">
	    	<NAME>Dress for Success</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC002</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC002</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC002</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Hmm, I really need to finish dressing my snowmen. Maybe you'd like to help out? Sure you would, you're my best friend! And best friends always help each other!
Take these items and go find my undecorated snowmen. I know there's one in Darby Field so you could start there. You can dress the snowmen however you like. I'll catch up with you in a bit. 
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
Have you decorated the snowmen yet? I'll be along shortly to help out.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Wow, you finished already? Thanks for helping out, you're a great friend!
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	
<!-- Tropic Week -->
	<QUEST ID="Q062a">
	    	<NAME>Colors of the Parrot</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC003</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC003</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC003</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Hi there! Have you ever seen a Parrot Feather? They are very pretty and colorful. I've been collecting them to use for crafts.
If you happen to come across any Parrot Feathers as you travel around Pandanda please pick them up and bring them to me. You'd be helping me out a lot and I'll be glad to pay you for them.
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
Have you had any luck finding the Parrot Feathers? I won't be able to complete my crafts without them.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Thank you! You're a great friend for getting these for me. 
Here's the coins as promised.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q062b">
	    	<NAME>Message in a Bottle</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC004</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC004</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC004</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Hey, how's the fishing going? I've heard rumors of Pandas sending messages across the sea by stuffing  parchment into a bottle and letting the waves carry it across the ocean. Wouldn't that be something!
If you're ever over at Coconut Beach and find some Bottled Messages floating out in the water, bring them to me and I'll give you some coins in return.
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
Have you found any Bottled Messages yet? Head over to Coconut Beach and walk along the water, I'm sure you'll find something!
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Well what do you know, looks like the rumors were true!
Thanks for your help, here's some coins as promised.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q062c">
	    	<NAME>Bury Me Treasure</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC007</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC007</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC007</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Hey there! You look like a Panda I can trust. I've got some treasure that I need buried for safe keeping. You up for some hard work? Of course you are. You do this for me and I'll make sure you get rewarded. 
I've marked out 5 locations across Pandanda where you should bury a treasure chest. 2 of them are at Coconut Beach. When you find an 'X' just dig a hole and drop in the treasure. But make sure no one's looking! Come back when you're done.
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
Have you buried that treasure yet? Make sure no one sees you. Kind of pointless to bury treasure if everyone knows where it is.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
All done eh? Great job! Here's some coins for your honesty.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	
<!-- Friendship Festival -->
	<QUEST ID="Q063a">
	    	<NAME>Cupcakes for My Friends</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC003</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC003</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC003</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Isn't the Friendship Festival wonderful? It's a great time to let your friends know how special they are to you. I made cupcakes for my friends but haven't been able to deliver all of them.
Would you do me a favor and hand out these cupcakes to Farmer Dan, Mr. Elmhurst, Tammy, Lisa, Jim, and Farmer Ned? Come see me when you're done.
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
Have you gotten a chance to deliver the cupcakes to my remaining friends? I don't want them to feel left out.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Thank you! Friends like you are what make the Friendship Festival so great!
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q063b">
	    	<NAME>A Gift for Izzy</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC004</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC004</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC012</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Hey, I was wondering if you could do a favor for me seeing as how we're such good friends. You know Izzy over at the Pet Store, right? Well, I'd like to get her something special to celebrate the festival. 
There's a rare fish called the Majestic Angelfish that I know she'd really like. You can probably catch one over at Coconut Beach. Thanks!
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
Did you catch the Majestic Angelfish yet? I know Izzy will really like it. 
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
What a nice surprise! I've been wanting a Majestic Angelfish for a while now. Joe is so thoughtful!
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q063c">
	    	<NAME>Gifts for Joe</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC012</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC012</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC004</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Hi, would you have time to help me with something? I have a Fishing Guide book for Joe but left it in the Parlour at the House on Misty Hill. 
Could you retrieve the book and pick up a Box of Chocolates then delilver them to Joe at the Fishing Hole for me? You can purchase the Box of Chocolates from Mr. Elmhurst on West Market Street. You're a true friend!
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
Were you able to find the Fishing Guide book at the House on Misty Hill? Don't forget to stop by Mr. Elmhurst to purchase a Box of Chocolates for Joe.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
What's this? A Fishing Guide and a Box of Chocolates? Wow, Izzy sure is nice!
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q063d">
	    	<NAME>Donut Delivery</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC009</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC009</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC009</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Greetings! I do hope you are enjoying the Friendship Festival. Might I ask a favor? I've got some delicious donuts that I'd like to distribute to my friends. 
Would you mind handing them out to Paige at Bear Hollow, Lisa at Shady Glen, Tammy on East Market St., Mr. McWiggles at the Ice Cream Parlor, Farmer Ned at Harvest Grove, and Questy Greybeard at the Tree House Lobby? Return to me afterwards to collect your reward.
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
Have you had the opportunity to deliver my donuts yet? I do hope you can hand them out before they get stale.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Splendid! Here's some coins for your generosity and assistance.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q064a">
	    	<NAME>Chocolate and Roses</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC007</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC007</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC003</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
How are you enjoying the Friendship Festival? Speaking of friendships, would you be able to help me out with something? I'd like to get a gift for Paige in Bear Hollow. 
Could you collect 5 Red Roses from Darby Field and deliver them with a Box of Chocolates to Paige for me? You can purchase a Box of Chocolates from Mr. Elmhurst on West Market Street. You'd be a real pal!
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
Were you able to find the Red Roses and get the Box of Chocolates? I sure hope Paige likes them.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Thank you! These are from Jim? He's a really nice Panda.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q064b">
	    	<NAME>Lost Cards</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC002</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC002</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC002</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Oh no, I need your help! I've lost a whole batch of Valentine Cards! I worked so hard on them and now they're gone! The must have fallen out of my bag. 
Could you go and look for them for me? You're such a good friend, I'm sure you could find them if you tried.
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
Did you find my Valentine Cards yet? I worked so hard on them. I really hope they arent lost forever.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
You found them! I knew you could do it! Thanks!
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q064c">
	    	<NAME>Be My Valentine</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC002</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC002</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC002</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Hey! Would you do me a favor since it's the Friendship Festival and you're such a good friend? I wrote a bunch of Valentine Cards and it'd be awesome if you could deliver them for me!
Let's see, I have one for Joe at the Fishing Hole, Steve on East Market Street, Jim on West Market Street, Fitch at Clothing Co., Paige in Bear Hollow, and Izzy at the Pet Shop. Let me know when you've handed them all out.
		</TEXTSTART>
	    	<TEXTACTIVE>
Have you delivered my Valentine Cards yet? I don't want people to think I forgot about them.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Did you finish? Thanks! I'm so glad we're friends!
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	
	
	<!-- Intro -->
	<QUEST ID="Q101">
	    	<NAME>Quest Tutorial</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC003</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC003</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC003</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Hi! I see you noticed the yellow 'Q' above my head. That indicates I have a quest for you. If you accept it, then it will be listed in your Quest Log. You can open your Quest Log by clicking the yellow Q on your menu bar. There you can see the details, requirements, and status of your quests.
If you're ready for a quest, I could use your help. I was reading in the Book Nook and forgot my book there. Would you mind picking it up and bringing it to me?
		</TEXTSTART>
		<TEXTACTIVE>Were you able to find my book? I think it had a brown cover.
You can enter the Book Nook up the steps to my left.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Thank you for getting my book for me!
As you travel around Pandanda Land, you will find other Pandas that have Quests and need your help. Good luck!
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	
	<!-- Intro -->
	<QUEST ID="Q110a">
	    	<NAME>Taming A Dragon (Part 1)</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC018</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC018</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC021</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Welcome! I see you have reached Level 50! That is no small accomplishment! I believe you have earned the right to learn the art of dragon taming. It is not an easy task but the reward is well worth the effort!
I would ask that you first speak with Trixie in Pawthorne Forest. She is very wise in the ways of dragons. Here, take this letter to her and she will guide you further.
		</TEXTSTART>
		<TEXTACTIVE>You will most likely find Trixie in Pawthorne Forest. Go there at once and show her the letter I gave you.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Hmm, Questy believes you are ready to tame your own dragon! I'm not so sure but I will defer to his judgment and help you nonetheless. 
The first thing you will need is a collection of rare gems. Take this list to Jim on West Market Street and he will explain how best to gather these rare gems.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q110b">
	    	<NAME>Taming A Dragon (Part 2)</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC021</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC021</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC007</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Hmm, Questy believes you are ready to tame your own dragon! I'm not so sure, but I will defer to his judgment and help you nonetheless. 
The first thing you will need is a collection of rare gems. Take this list to Jim on West Market Street and he will explain how best to gather these rare gems.
		</TEXTSTART>
		<TEXTACTIVE>Take the list of rare gems to Jim on West Market Street. He can help you.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Ah, this is quite the list! This wouldn't have anything to do with dragons would it? Not really any of my business I suppose.  
These gems can all be found in Pandanda Land, but won't be found easily. You've gathered gems for me before so just go out and do your best. Come back when you've got them all.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q110c">
	    	<NAME>Taming A Dragon (Part 3)</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC007</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC007</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC007</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Ah, this is quite the list! This wouldn't have anything to do with dragons would it? Not really any of my business I suppose.  
These gems can all be found in Pandanda Land, but won't be found easily. You've gathered gems for me before so just go out and do your best. Come back when you've got them all.
		</TEXTSTART>
		<TEXTACTIVE>Have you found the gems yet? They could be anywhere around Pandanda Land.  Well, except not indoors of course.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Well look at that! These are beautiful. I'll get these polished up for you but you'll need a chest to carry them all in.
Take this blueprint over to Steve on East Market Street. He should be able to build a nice sturdy chest for you. 
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q110d">
	    	<NAME>Taming A Dragon (Part 4)</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC007</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC007</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC006</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Well look at that! These are beautiful. I'll get these polished up for you but you'll need a chest to carry them all in.
Take this blueprint over to Steve on East Market Street. He should be able to build a nice sturdy chest for you. 
		</TEXTSTART>
		<TEXTACTIVE>While I polish these gems up, head over to Steve on East Market Street to see about that chest.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
What's this? You're in need of a chest eh? Well I could build one for you but I'll need some wood first. 
Head over to Pawthorne Forest and gather up some fresh cut wood and I'll be able to complete your chest.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q110e">
	    	<NAME>Taming A Dragon (Part 5)</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC006</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC006</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC006</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
What's this? You're in need of a chest eh? Well I could build one for you but I'll need some wood first. 
Head over to Pawthorne Forest and gather up some fresh cut wood and I'll be able to complete your chest.
		</TEXTSTART>
		<TEXTACTIVE>Did you get that wood from Pawthorne Forest yet? Can't make a chest without wood.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
So, you've returned with the wood? I've just completed your chest as specified by the blueprints you gave me. It's very sturdy and should hold whatever you need it to.
I suppose you should head back to Jim now to fill it up! 
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q110f">
	    	<NAME>Taming A Dragon (Part 6)</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC006</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC006</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC007</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
So, you've returned with the wood? I've just completed your chest as specified by the blueprints you gave me. It's very sturdy and should hold whatever you need it to.
I supose you should head back to Jim now to fill it up! 
		</TEXTSTART>
		<TEXTACTIVE>That's one of the best chests I've ever crafted. Head over to Jim to fill it up.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Hello again. I see you've got the chest built. I'm done polishing the gems so let's load them into the chest and see if it holds together. 
There you go. Take the chest and gems back to Trixie and good luck!
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q110g">
	    	<NAME>Taming A Dragon (Part 7)</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC007</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC007</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC021</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Hello again. I see you've got the chest built. I'm done polishing the gems so let's load them into the chest and see if it holds together. 
There you go. Take the chest and gems back to Trixie and good luck!
		</TEXTSTART>
		<TEXTACTIVE>Take the chest and gems back to Trixie. You'll probably find her in Pawthorne Forest.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
You have returned with the gems! Excellent work! They will be very useful later on. However, more items are needed before you will be ready to tame a full grown dragon.
The next thing you must do is prepare a large feast. Take this list to Fishy Joe and he will help you prepare it.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q110h">
	    	<NAME>Taming A Dragon (Part 8)</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC021</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC021</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC004</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
You have returned with the gems! Excellent work! They will be very useful later on. However, more items are needed before you will be ready to tame a full grown dragon.
The next thing you must do is prepare a large feast. Take this list to Fishy Joe and he will help you prepare it.
		</TEXTSTART>
		<TEXTACTIVE>Take the list to Fishy Joe at the Fishing Hole, he will help you make a feast fit for a dragon.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Hey there. So you need help making a large feast for a dragon? Sounds dangerous but I'll help you out. Let's see. 
You'll need 3 Large Salmon, 2 Large Trout, and 2 Large Catfish. The trout and catfish can be found here but the best salmon are caught on Coconut Beach. Come back and see me when you're done.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q110i">
	    	<NAME>Taming A Dragon (Part 9)</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC004</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC004</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC004</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Hey there. So you need help making a large feast for a dragon? Sounds dangerous but I'll help you out. Let's see. 
You'll need 3 Large Salmon, 2 Large Trout, and 2 Large Catfish. The trout and catfish can be found here but the best salmon are caught on Coconut Beach. Come back and see me when you're done.
		</TEXTSTART>
		<TEXTACTIVE>Go catch those fish and I'll prepare the other items for the large feast.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
You caught them all? Great! Let me just clean them here and add them to this arrangement. I hope this is satisfactory. Dragons can be very picky when it comes to food.
They are all done. Take this back to Trixie as quickly as you can. I'd hate for a dragon to catch you with it before you're fully prepared.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q110j">
	    	<NAME>Taming A Dragon (Part 10)</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC004</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC004</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC021</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
You caught them all? Great! Let me just clean them here and add them to this arrangement. I hope this is satisfactory. Dragons can be very picky when it comes to food.
They are all done. Take this back to Trixie as quickly as you can. I'd hate for a dragon to catch you with it before you're fully prepared.
		</TEXTSTART>
		<TEXTACTIVE>Be careful carrying that feast around. You don't want a dragon to swoop down and take you away with it.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
You are making good progress. The chest full of rare gems and the large feast are all prepared. 
The last thing you'll need is a Beacon Staff which will summon a dragon. Questy Greybeard will have a Beacon Staff for you.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q110k">
	    	<NAME>Taming A Dragon (Part 11)</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC021</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC021</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC018</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
You are making good progress. The chest full of rare gems and the large feast are all prepared. 
The last thing you'll need is a Beacon Staff which will summon a dragon. Questy Greybeard will have a Beacon Staff for you. Take this letter to Questy detailing your progress.
		</TEXTSTART>
		<TEXTACTIVE>Take the letter to Questy and he will provide you with a Beacon Staff.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Ah, young Panda, I see you have prepared yourself for the dragon summoning under Trixie's tutelage. Here, take this Beacon Staff and return to Trixie once more. She will give you final instructions on summoning a dragon. 
I know when the time comes, you will be brave, and honor all the Pandas that have come before you who have had the courage to bond with the dragon kin.
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q110l">
	    	<NAME>Taming A Dragon (Part 12)</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC018</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC018</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC021</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
Ah, young Panda, I see you have prepared yourself for the dragon summoning under Trixie's tutelage. Here, take this Beacon Staff and return to Trixie once more. She will give you final instructions on summoning a dragon. 
I know when the time comes, you will be brave, and honor all the Pandas that have come before you who have had the courage to bond with the dragon kin.
		</TEXTSTART>
		<TEXTACTIVE>Return to Trixie with the Beacon Staff and prepare yourself for the summoning!
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
You are nearly ready. But first I must imbue this Beacon Staff to summon either a Blue Dragon or a Grey Dragon. You may only summon one or the other, not both. Choose wisely!
When you have decided which dragon you wish to summon, speak with me again. 
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	
	<QUEST ID="Q111">
	    	<NAME>Summon a Grey Dragon</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC021</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC021</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC022</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
The time has come to summon a dragon. I will imbue the beacon staff to call forth a Grey Dragon.  If you wish to summon a Blue Dragon instead, do not accept this quest.
You must take the Imbued Beacon Staff, Dragon Feast, and Chest of Rare Gems  to Coconut Beach. There you will find a marking in the sand. Place these items and hopefully a dragon will come and decide not to eat you. Good luck!		
		</TEXTSTART>
		<TEXTACTIVE>Take the Imbued Beacon Staff, Dragon Feast, and Chest of Rare Gems  to Coconut Beach and place them on the marking in the sand.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Who is it that summons me? You seek to buy my loyalty with these gifts? It is a brave Panda that dares to tempt a dragon! 
However, you must know something of dragon lore to provide such gifts and I sense  your heart is pure. Yes, you are a special Panda. Come, you may ride on my back and we will have many adventures together!
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>

	<QUEST ID="Q112">
	    	<NAME>Summon a Blue Dragon</NAME>
	    	<START>NPC021</START>
	    	<ACTIVE>NPC021</ACTIVE>
	    	<END>NPC022</END>
	    	<TEXTSTART>
The time has come to summon a dragon. I will imbue the beacon staff to call forth a Blue Dragon.  If you wish to summon a Grey Dragon instead, do not accept this quest.
You must take the Imbued Beacon Staff, Dragon Feast, and Chest of Rare Gems  to Coconut Beach. There you will find a marking in the sand. Place these items and hopefully a dragon will come and decide not to eat you. Good luck!		
		</TEXTSTART>
		<TEXTACTIVE>Take the Imbued Beacon Staff, Dragon Feast, and Chest of Rare Gems  to Coconut Beach and place them on the marking in the sand.
		</TEXTACTIVE>
	    	<TEXTEND>
Who is it that summons me? You seek to buy my loyalty with these gifts? It is a brave Panda that dares to tempt a dragon! 
However, you must know something of dragon lore to provide such gifts and I sense  your heart is pure. Yes, you are a special Panda. Come, you may ride on my back and we will have many adventures together!
		</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	
	
	
	<QUEST ID="Q049a">
	    <NAME>Test 2!</NAME>
	    <START>NPC003</START>
	    <ACTIVE>NPC003</ACTIVE>
	    <END>NPC003</END>
	    <TEXTSTART>panda power</TEXTSTART>
	    <TEXTACTIVE>click me</TEXTACTIVE>
	    <TEXTEND>panda power</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	<QUEST ID="Q050a">
	    <NAME>Test!</NAME>
	    <START>NPC003</START>
	    <ACTIVE>NPC003</ACTIVE>
	    <END>NPC003</END>
	    <TEXTSTART>
	   test
	    </TEXTSTART>
	    <TEXTACTIVE>did you find it?</TEXTACTIVE>
	    <TEXTEND>You found it!</TEXTEND>
	</QUEST>
	
</QUESTS>